

Hello I'm David Hayrapetyan

Yerevan +37494035534 networkdavit@gmail.com https://davidhayrapetyan.online

Skills

Python, Java, JavaScript, Ruby, HTML5, CSS3, SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL

Flask, React, Docker, API, Amazon AWS, Linux

Experience

FEBRUARY 2019 - PRESENT

Skyeng - English Tutor

- Working as an English Tutor with individual students
- Ensure that my students are happy and have progress
- Find methods to approach any student and ensure satisfaction from every lesson

DECEMBER 2018 - PRESENT

Freelance - Freelance Web/Software Developer

- Working on various freelancing platforms and through connections in real life
- Building websites//landing pages/blogs/personal websites
- Making GUI applications/scripts and automating tasks

OCTOBER 2018 - JANUARY 2019

Freelance - Journalist/SMM

- Writing articles for an independent publisher about Opera
- Advertising events through social media
- Growing our audience through social media

Education

SEPTEMBER 2016 - MAY 2020

American University of Armenia, Yerevan - Bachelor's degree

About

Hi! I'm David, English Tutor, Freelance Developer, and Cybersecurity Researcher. I have over 3 years of experience developing websites and applications, automating tasks, performing penetration testing, and securing web applications.

I am passionate about development and cybersecurity. I enjoy solving problems that I encounter during my free time, but also love to learn new technologies that are useful for me and my work. One of my goals is to become better at what I do and develop as much as I can in everything that I touch and work on.

Hobbies

Music, piano, skateboarding, photography, philosophy, video games, art.